Harsha Jagadish

Tech lead & Junior solutions Architect at Mobinius

jagadish.harsha@gmail.com

Summary

A front end engineer and tech lead with expertise in Javascript, NativeScript, angular 6, Ionic 3, React JS and ember JS. I develop product centric web applications and hybrid mobile application. Currently working on AR kit with NativeScript on the mobile side and using awe.js to get MR on the web along with OpenCV for object recognition.

Experience

Tech lead at Mobinius

October 2015 - Present

I am responsible to head several teams, from UI to backend, and ensure project success by leading on the development side as well as the delivery side of the project. I handle the documentations for the project acceptance to handover to clients.

Senior UI Engineer at Cisco

December 2013 - October 2015 (1 year 11 months)

I lead a team of UI developers from Bangalore and France working on a critical project for CISCO.

UI Team Lead at Cisco

December 2013 - October 2015 (1 year 11 months)

I was responsible to head the UI team in creating the UI designs and UI development for all the projects that Cisco handled.

Front end Engineer at Vaakya Technologies

October 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 3 months)

I was responsible to create the user interface for Vaakya.com and for other web applications by Vaakya.

Web Developer at Amaltas Retail Pvt Ltd

December 2011 - October 2012 (11 months)

I have designed and developed the e-commerce website for LUSH,an international cosmetic brand. I am currently maintaining their website www.lushindia.com,a website I designed and developed.

Software developer

September 2010 - December 2011 (1 year 4 months)

I created an OCR for local language like Kannad using Java. I created the OCR for Hindi as well as the sanskrit. I designed adn developed more then 4 websites for various clients.

Education

PES School of Engineering Bachelor's degree, Computer and Information Sciences, General, 2006 - 2010 vijaya high school bangalore Pcmb, 2001 - 2004

Harsha Jagadish

Tech lead & Junior solutions Architect at Mobinius

jagadish.harsha@gmail.com



Contact Harsha on LinkedIn